If we look at the genital tubercle, it will give rise to the glans and the body of the penis.
生殖結節を見ると、それは亀頭と陰茎体になります。
In females, it will give rise to the glans and the body of the clitoris.
女性の場合、それは亀頭と陰核体になります。
The urogenital sinus will give rise to the penile urethra and the vestibule
尿生殖洞は、陰茎尿道と前庭になります。
of the vagina in females.
女性の膣の。
The urethral fold will give rise to the penis and the penile urethra and the labia minora,
尿道ひだは陰茎と陰茎尿道、そして小陰唇になります。
labia,
唇、
while the labioscrotal fold will give rise to the scrotum and the labia majora.
一方、陰唇陰嚢ひだは陰嚢と大陰唇になります。
There is a masculine and a feminine.
男性と女性があります。
This is where all the closure under the median line occurs.
それは、正中線の下のすべての閉鎖です。
First, we see the separation between the cloaca and the rectum.
まず、総排泄腔と直腸の分離が見られます。
Here, we see what is called the clitoris developing the labia minora, the labia majora.
そこには、小陰唇と大陰唇を発達させる陰核と呼ばれるものが見られます。
And what does that correspond to in men?
そして、それは男性では何に対応しますか？
The clitoris becomes the glans and the penis.
陰核は亀頭と陰茎になります。
And here, the labia minora, the closure here, it's the scrotum closing.
そしてここで、小陰唇、ここでの閉鎖は、閉鎖する陰嚢です。
And then the labia minora and labia majora that are forming here.
そして、ここに描かれている小陰唇と大陰唇。
they are here this differentiation
それらはここにあるこの分化です
begins when the liver and my
肝臓と私のものが
adrenal glands grow and start to move
副腎が成長し、そこから離れていくときに始まります。
to the side, you see, well, there we are
側面を見てください、私たちはそこにいます
between the fifth and eighth week, I start to have a posterior view.
5週目から8週目の間に、私は視界を持ち始めます
we have the falciform ligament, the round ligament,
後方には、鎌状靭帯、円索靭帯があります。
continuing with the median fold here and
ここにある正中ひだと連続しています。
inside here this white line which
そして、ここにあるこの白い線の中には、
is the continuity of this tissue, of that line. That's why when
この組織、この線の連続性です。だから、
it's finished, this line closes and contains the
それが終わると、この線は閉じ、その中に
story. It is the
歴史が含まれます。それは
result of all this movement. When this is finished, it means everything
このすべての動きの結果です。これが終わると、すべてが
behind is done. If we go a little further now, there is a
後ろにあります。もう少し進むと、そこには
in the shape that is forming
形成される形の中に
in relation to my face
私の顔に関して
that is settling here, the nose.
ここに配置される鼻。
You remember, the nose developing
覚えていますか、発達する鼻
like that, like a uterus.
このように、子宮のように。
My sternum developing
発達する私の胸骨
like the uterine system and the whole system
子宮系とすべての系のように
that develops towards my median line.
私の正中線に向かって発達します。
Both sternal,
胸骨も、
both facial, and also here.
顔も、そしてここも。
It's the entire closure
それはすべての閉鎖です
of the anterior median line.
前正中線の。
Gonadal sex to the ovary.
生殖腺の性別は緑色です。
Here, I have no secret.
そこには秘密はありません。
of androgen, Wolff's body
アンドロゲン、ホルッフの体
will regress, while here
それは退行するでしょう、一方ここでは
it will become the epididymis
それは精巣上体になるでしょう
ductus deferens, seminal vesicle and ejaculatory
精管、精嚢、管
duct,
射精管、
the Müllerian duct becomes the fallopian tube, uterus
ミュラー管は子宮卵管になります
while the Müllerian duct will
一方、ミュラー管は
regress in males, the urogenital
男性では退行し、尿生殖洞は
sinus remains
開いたままです、男性では閉じます、
open, it closes in males,
前庭、小陰唇
vestibule, labia minora
それは
which come from
内胚葉から来て、尿道を与えるでしょう
the endoderm, will give rise to the urethra
そして周囲の前立腺部分。
and the surrounding prostatic part.
生殖結節は男性では陰茎になり、女性では陰核になります。
The genital tubercle becomes the penis and the clitoris in females.
そして外性器のレベルでは、生殖隆起があります
And at the level of the external organs, you have the genital swellings
それは小陰唇と大陰唇と呼ばれるものを形成するでしょう。
which will form what are called the labia minora and labia majora.
忘れないでください、私たちは頭の中に葛藤を抱えたままではいられません。
Don't forget, we can't stay with a conflict in our head.
長くはとどまれません。
We can't stay long.
では、何が起こるのでしょうか？
So, what happens?
もしある時点でうまくいかないなら、どこかでそれを身体化しなければなりません、
If at some point, it's not going well, we have to somatize it somewhere,
その象徴性に応じて。
according to its symbolism.
私たちはそれをその領域に置きます。
We will put it in its realm.
尿生殖器、代謝、律動、または神経感覚。
Urogenital, metabolic, rhythmic or neurosensory.
このようにして私たちはそれに応答します。
That's how we're going to respond to it.
分離の葛藤、皮膚、そのようなもの。